Guide to the Colgate University Department of History records A1092
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
Colgate University Department of History records
1892-2001
A1092
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
2 Cubic feet
Colgate University. Department of History.
Access to Collection
Collection is open for research; however, special restrictions may apply to portions of this collection in accordance with the Colgate University Archives policy on restricted records. Please contact Special Collections and University Archives for further information.
Annual reports.; Correspondence.; Foreign study.; History--Study and teaching.; Memorandums.; Syllabi.
- Achievement test - History 102, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Administrative positions, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Advanced Placement questionnaire and responses, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Advanced Placement tests conference, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- American Historical Association, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Budget, 1958-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Budget, 1946-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Carnegie European Summer Research Awards, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Concentrators, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Concentrators, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Courses, schedules, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Curriculum, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Development and projects, 1953, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Examinations, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Faculty, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Ford Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- General information, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- General information, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- General information, 1947-1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- General information, 1937-1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Courses and department information, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Department of Health, Education, & Welfare, History evaluation, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Honors Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Humanities report, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Independent Study projects - History, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- History internship, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- International Honors program, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- History Department - January Intersession, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- History Department - Lectures, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1947-1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- N.Y. State History Conference, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Department memos, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Memos, 1947-1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Department meeting minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Navarette's class registers, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
- History Department physical needs, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Post graduation plans of History majors, 1969 May (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Post graduation plans of History majors, 1970 May (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Post-graduate plans - Class of 1971 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Schedules, 1957-1967 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Selesky, Harold correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Task Force on 12 Month Year, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Julius Turner award, 1949-1956 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Travel expense vouchers, 1949-1953 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- List of visual aids, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Course materials, 1892-1948 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Courses and future careers, 1948-1959 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Memos and programs, 1966-1973 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Correspondence and memos, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Courses, correspondence, and memos, 1947-1963 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Syllabi, 1956-1981
  - Syllabi, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Syllabi, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Syllabi, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Syllabi, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Syllabi, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Syllabi, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Syllabi, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Syllabi, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Syllabi, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Syllabi, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Syllabi, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Syllabi, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Syllabi, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Syllabi, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Syllabi, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Syllabi, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Syllabi, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
- London History Study Group, 1966-1974
  - London History Study Group - Materials regarding Askew's and Blackton's groups, 1966-1976 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - London History Study Group (Director Rockwood), 1968 Fall (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - London History Study Group special events, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - London History Study Group - Seminar I: Research Project (Director Rockwood), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - London History Study Group (Director Rockwood), 1971 Fall (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - London History Study Group - Cumberland Lodge program, 1971 Fall (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - London History Study Group (Director Rockwood), 1974 Fall (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - London History Study Group - Hist. 342: Great Britain in Modern Times (Rockwood), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Yugoslavia trip, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Summer session in Great Britain, 1975
  - Summer session in Great Britain (Rockwood), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Summer session in Great Britain general information, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Summer session in Great Britain - Stirling planning, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Summer session in Great Britain - Oxford, academic file, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Summer session curriculum, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- History Department comprehensive examinations, 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- History Department comprehensive examinations, 1936-1942 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Course materials, undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Annual Reports, 1941-2001
  - Annual Reports, 1941-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 100)